<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Faiza Ahmed’s Artistic Ode to Women Freedom Fighters &#8211; Annualreport2018 Acciona</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/faiza-ahmeds-artistic-ode-to-women-freedom-fighters/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 11:23:50 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/live-favicon.jpg</url>
	<title>Faiza Ahmed’s Artistic Ode to Women Freedom Fighters &#8211; Annualreport2018 Acciona</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Faiza Ahmed’s Artistic Ode to Women Freedom Fighters</title>
		<link>/faiza-ahmeds-artistic-ode-to-women-freedom-fighters/</link>
					<comments>/faiza-ahmeds-artistic-ode-to-women-freedom-fighters/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Womans Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Faiza Ahmed’s Artistic Ode to Women Freedom Fighters]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=652</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Reputed designer and artist, Faiza Ahmed — proprietor and fashion designer of the clothing brand Manas — has decided to combine these mediums and feature them in her design collection. On 8 February 2024, Manas unveiled a line of saris...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Reputed designer and artist, Faiza Ahmed — proprietor and fashion designer of the clothing brand Manas — has decided to combine these mediums and feature them in her design collection. On 8 February 2024, Manas unveiled a line of saris at the Banani outlet of GoDeshi that pays homage to the women freedom fighters of Bangladesh.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The inaugural ceremony was attended by a group of connoisseurs, including renowned painter, Kanak Chanpa Chakma. Faiza Ahmed drew inspiration from the sculpture Khalishpur 71, curated by Fuleshwari Priyonandini, daughter of Ferdousi Priyabhashini.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Faiza Ahmed’s artistic ode to women freedom fighters</strong><br />
In her heartfelt statement, Ahmed shared the ethos behind her collection: &#8220;From the beginning, we have prioritised the arts and culture of Bangladesh in the thematic saris of Manas. Last year, I included the lyrics of the song, &#8216;O Amar Desher Mati&#8217; in my collection. However, I wanted to go deeper and work with a theme deeply connected to our roots.&#8221;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">She elaborated on her inspiration drawn from Fuleshwari Priyonandini&#8217;s work, &#8220;I was thinking about the contribution of women to our Liberation War and consequently, a sculpture by my good friend Fuleshwari caught my attention.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/faiza-ahmeds-artistic-ode-to-women-freedom-fighters/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
