<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>admin &#8211; Annualreport2018 Acciona</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/admin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link></link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 28 Feb 2024 11:24:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.4.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2023/07/live-favicon.jpg</url>
	<title>admin &#8211; Annualreport2018 Acciona</title>
	<link></link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Faiza Ahmed’s Artistic Ode to Women Freedom Fighters</title>
		<link>/faiza-ahmeds-artistic-ode-to-women-freedom-fighters/</link>
					<comments>/faiza-ahmeds-artistic-ode-to-women-freedom-fighters/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:16:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Womans Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Faiza Ahmed’s Artistic Ode to Women Freedom Fighters]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=652</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Reputed designer and artist, Faiza Ahmed — proprietor and fashion designer of the clothing brand Manas — has decided to combine these mediums and feature them in her design collection. On 8 February 2024, Manas unveiled a line of saris...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Reputed designer and artist, Faiza Ahmed — proprietor and fashion designer of the clothing brand Manas — has decided to combine these mediums and feature them in her design collection. On 8 February 2024, Manas unveiled a line of saris at the Banani outlet of GoDeshi that pays homage to the women freedom fighters of Bangladesh.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">The inaugural ceremony was attended by a group of connoisseurs, including renowned painter, Kanak Chanpa Chakma. Faiza Ahmed drew inspiration from the sculpture Khalishpur 71, curated by Fuleshwari Priyonandini, daughter of Ferdousi Priyabhashini.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Faiza Ahmed’s artistic ode to women freedom fighters</strong><br />
In her heartfelt statement, Ahmed shared the ethos behind her collection: &#8220;From the beginning, we have prioritised the arts and culture of Bangladesh in the thematic saris of Manas. Last year, I included the lyrics of the song, &#8216;O Amar Desher Mati&#8217; in my collection. However, I wanted to go deeper and work with a theme deeply connected to our roots.&#8221;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">She elaborated on her inspiration drawn from Fuleshwari Priyonandini&#8217;s work, &#8220;I was thinking about the contribution of women to our Liberation War and consequently, a sculpture by my good friend Fuleshwari caught my attention.&#8221;</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/faiza-ahmeds-artistic-ode-to-women-freedom-fighters/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hair And Beauty Fest 2024 A New Beginning By BSOAB</title>
		<link>/hair-and-beauty-fest-2024-a-new-beginning-by-bsoab/</link>
					<comments>/hair-and-beauty-fest-2024-a-new-beginning-by-bsoab/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:14:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Womans Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Hair And Beauty Fest 2024 A New Beginning By BSOAB]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=649</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[The inaugural Hair and Beauty Fest 2024, organised by the Beauty Service Owners Association of Bangladesh (BSOAB), unfolded as a two-day extravaganza on 11 and 12 February that&#8217;s successfully made a mark on the landscape of beauty and fashion in...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">The inaugural Hair and Beauty Fest 2024, organised by the Beauty Service Owners Association of Bangladesh (BSOAB), unfolded as a two-day extravaganza on 11 and 12 February that&#8217;s successfully made a mark on the landscape of beauty and fashion in the country. The aim was to gather, connect and motivate beauty enthusiasts from all over the country and nudge them towards their passion. As Kaniz Almas Khan, President of BSOAB, had remarked during the official press conference, &#8220;The Hair and Beauty Fest is our commitment to empowering women in the beauty sector, providing them with the tools and confidence to forge independent careers.&#8221; This fresh idea, held under the banner of creativity and inclusivity, served as a dynamic platform for beauty enthusiasts, professionals and industry experts to get together, network, and celebrate the artistry and creativity that are present in the beauty business currently.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">At the heart of the Hair and Beauty Fest 2024 was a vibrant fashion show, where the latest trends and styles in hair and makeup were showcased with unparalleled flair and finesse. Makeup and hair artists from within Bangladesh as well as abroad showcased their creative prowess on the runway, leaving viewers in amazement with their stunning looks and remarkable beauty makeovers.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Hair and Beauty Fest 2024: A new beginning by BSOAB</strong><br />
Beyond the runway, the fest featured live demonstrations of hair and makeup techniques by leading beauty experts, providing attendees with invaluable insights into the art and science of beauty. From the latest hairstyle techniques and hacks to creating a flawless base, these sessions offered a first-hand glimpse into the innovative techniques and trends shaping the beauty landscape today. A Q&amp;A round after each session not only helped attendees from different parts of the country to have a one-on-one interaction with the experts, but also served as an ice-breaker, promoting easy communication among them. Debra Robinson and Jennifer Quartermaine, who have been running their own vocational training on makeup and hairstyles in Mymensingh for the past 14 years, think that this is the first step to a revolutionary change in the beauty industry of Bangladesh. &#8220;The free flow of information and technique that this event is promoting is unprecedented,&#8221; stated Quartermaine. Seconding her opinion, Robinson said, &#8220;Though many of our students work in Mymensingh, their young dream is always to make a name for themselves here in Dhaka. I think networking through events like this one will take them several steps forward in that dream.&#8221;</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Hair and Beauty Fest 2024: A new beginning by BSOAB</strong><br />
Another part of this event featured an extensive exhibition showcasing the latest products, tools, and technologies revolutionising the beauty industry, where attendees had the opportunity to explore and experience the latest advancements in beauty first-hand. A gorgeous award ceremony graced the event, honouring the visionary personalities of the beauty industry. These awards not only recognised and celebrated their success, but also served as a testament to their dedication and innovation, driving the beauty industry forward in Bangladesh.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Hair and Beauty Fest 2024: A new beginning by BSOAB</strong><br />
The first-ever Hair and Beauty Fest 2024 was a resounding success, redefining the landscape of beauty and fashion in Bangladesh. From its dazzling fashion show to its insightful demonstrations and engaging discussions, the event showcased the immense talent, creativity, and potential within the beauty industry, while fostering collaboration, community-building, and empowerment.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/hair-and-beauty-fest-2024-a-new-beginning-by-bsoab/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Coco Chanel’s Greatest Inventions</title>
		<link>/coco-chanels-greatest-inventions/</link>
					<comments>/coco-chanels-greatest-inventions/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:12:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Womans Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Coco Chanel’s Greatest Inventions]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=646</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Coco Chanel is an indomitable name in the world of fashion. Yet, the extent of her influence may surprise many, as numerous globally acclaimed fashion pieces stem from her original designs. Ranging from iconic handbags to timeless tweed coats, here&#8217;s...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Coco Chanel is an indomitable name in the world of fashion. Yet, the extent of her influence may surprise many, as numerous globally acclaimed fashion pieces stem from her original designs. Ranging from iconic handbags to timeless tweed coats, here&#8217;s a comprehensive catalogue of Coco&#8217;s innovative contributions to fashion.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Tweed Suit</strong><br />
In an attempt to combine masculine and feminine fashion, Coco Chanel used tweed in her suits all the way in the 1920s. This invariably became one of her biggest contributions to the world of fashion. While not historically considered to be luxurious, tweed suits have found fans in celebrities such as Princess Diana and Anna Wintour among others.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>The Li&#8217;l Black Dress</strong><br />
Another product of the 1920s, the little black dress was Chanel&#8217;s brainchild and what a blessed one at that! Simple, versatile, and timeless, the outfit is known as &#8220;Chanel&#8217;s Ford,&#8221; carrying its weight over the decades and well into the modern times.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>The Pearl Necklace</strong><br />
An ace fashion designer, Chanel was also a top-rate jewellery connoisseur. She was the first to combine fine jewellery with fashionable clothes, completing the outfit. While she had hired herself an expensive Italian jewellery designer, Fulco di Verdura, the idea of the pearl necklace is widely believed to have come from Coco herself.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>The Handbag</strong><br />
Before the 1920s, the world of fashion had never known a single handbag. There were only clutches that had to be carried with both hands. Inspired by strap handles used in soldiers&#8217; bags, Coco Chanel designed her own handbag that sported the iconic Chanel pop up lid — and thank goodness — straps!</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>The Chanel No. 5</strong><br />
Prepared for Coco by her perfumer Ernest Beaux, the Chanel No. 5 is an exquisite fragrance that was brought out under the brand in the 1920s. The perfume was called Chanel No. 5 because it was the fifth sample out of the ten that were created. A particular favourite of Marilyn Monroe, the scent continues to be one of the bestselling perfumes across the world.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Women&#8217;s Pants</strong><br />
In a world filled with exquisite dresses and skirts for women, if any designer was gutsy enough to go for pants, it was Chanel. She loved wearing her partner&#8217;s pants as they gave her freedom of mobility, and she found them comfortable and stylish enough to make them commercially viable for women. It&#8217;s all thanks to Coco that women nowadays wear everything from pyjamas to formal pants.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Slingbacks and Ballet Flats</strong><br />
From slingbacks to ballet flats, both the iconic shoes that females around the world wear different variations of, are handiworks of Coco Chanel. If the slingback is all the rage on the ramp and great for occasional wear, the ballet flat is its more practical sister that one can play sports in!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/coco-chanels-greatest-inventions/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Celebrating The Colours Of Falgun</title>
		<link>/celebrating-the-colours-of-falgun/</link>
					<comments>/celebrating-the-colours-of-falgun/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:09:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Womans Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Celebrating The Colours Of Falgun]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=643</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Falgun is the time to feel your best. Everywhere around, flowers are blooming and people are more often than not, in jovial moods. The fashion game is also at its peak because the fashionistas have already stacked away their dull...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Falgun is the time to feel your best. Everywhere around, flowers are blooming and people are more often than not, in jovial moods. The fashion game is also at its peak because the fashionistas have already stacked away their dull and dreary winter wear and stocking up on strikingly beautiful and equally bold fashion wear. This is also the season when the ladies of Bangladesh start wearing more traditional clothes like saris and kameezes. There is just something in the air that screams beauty and fashion. To the people who are not a big fan of traditional wear, there are always agreeable alternatives and today we discuss those.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Celebrating the colours of Falgun</strong><br />
<strong>Photo: Sazzad Ibne Sayed</strong><br />
The main thing that you must remember about spring is that it is the season of colours. The category of clothing does not matter much, but the colours do. It must be addressed and I cannot stress enough, how very important it is to incorporate colours back into our dull and dreary lives. The soothing pastels, fruity colours, corals, vibrant reds, mystique blues, and ultimately the fiery oranges must be loaded in our closet. There are no hard and fast rules that for a traditional garb. What one can do is also experiment with boho chic items or even go subtle with plain jumpsuits, skirts, or flowy tops paired with jeans.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;"><strong>Celebrating the colours of Falgun</strong><br />
<strong>Photo: Sazzad Ibne Sayed</strong><br />
There is only one rule at the end of it all, the colours must pop out and must make any other person associating with you feel the depth of the brightness. They must smile and they will, when they see you in a lime green jumpsuit, with beaded hoops as earrings and a tiny rose tucked in the side parting of your tresses. The idea is to be contagious with the feelings of optimism. And the best part is, there is no necessity to spend expansively on any item. The gist is to be colourful – it is to be bright and beautiful. That&#8217;s it.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/celebrating-the-colours-of-falgun/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>A Day In The Life Of a Social Butterfly</title>
		<link>/a-day-in-the-life-of-a-social-butterfly/</link>
					<comments>/a-day-in-the-life-of-a-social-butterfly/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[admin]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Feb 2024 13:03:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Womans Lifestyle]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[A Day In The Life Of a Social Butterfly]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=640</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Another winter, another dozen weddings to attend. The pomp and circumstance surrounding a wedding is on steroids these days in Dhaka and you are here for it! Having secured your invitation to the most extravagant ones of the season, your...]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[<p style="text-align: justify;">Another winter, another dozen weddings to attend. The pomp and circumstance surrounding a wedding is on steroids these days in Dhaka and you are here for it! Having secured your invitation to the most extravagant ones of the season, your outfits have been sorted, each more extravagant than the last. Sure, a few of them have been borrowed from those wealthy friends with a closet to envy, some are first-grade replicas of designer outfits from Kolkata and a few are knock-offs from, well, Gawsia but no one will know, you are sure of it.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Starting from sangeet, dala exchange, dance rehearsals, dala exchange, holud, wedding, reception — there is not an end to these festivities but you are armed, guns blazing! Between friends, a few of these outfits might upstage the bride but who really cares — a girl must look her absolute best, shine bright like a diamond and dance the night away in her Sabyasachi and Masaba! After all, getting invited to these events was no mean feat since you barely know the hosts and had to pull some serious strings to ensure your presence.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">A girl has got to make the most out of such events by looking her absolute best! Hastily, you clear out your phone memory, making space for those few thousand pictures you will be taking of yourself and your friends. Amidst the blinding lights of chandeliers, opulent wedding décor, and high shine of your cubic zirconia necklace you might miss greeting the bride and groom entirely, but who really cares about them as long as you have managed to snag a much-coveted selfie with the imported star performers!</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">Dancing your heart out to their mashups and hit numbers, you have a ball with other random guests you do not know, alongside taking pictures and not missing a moment! Not to mention the denizens of high society who barely know you, but a selfie with them is sure to elevate your social status to that of a big shot hobnobbing with the elites.</p>
<p style="text-align: justify;">So, with your mile-long Huda lashes aflutter, your razor-sharp cut crease and contours that bring out your non-existent cheekbones you arrive in style. And all the while, as you upload pictures and selfies in real time, your smartwatch is on fire, pinging non-stop — likes, hearts, emojis, and comments galore — reminding you what a smashing success your clever endeavours have been this season!</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/a-day-in-the-life-of-a-social-butterfly/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
